casinobellini.com 2014-07-02

# Casino Bellini: Privacy Statement

## Casino Bellini and its affiliate firms are dedicated to honoring and securing your privacy.

This statement divulges the data assembled by Casino Bellini.

## Web Site operations info

Our site automatically records Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of visitors reaching our site as part of site operations as well as for our own analysis of site traffic. We do NOT record any visitor's e-mail address.

## Mail policy

We do not tolerate spam.   
We received your consent for communication via email.   
We send you promotional emails and updates until such time as you inform us that you do not wish to continue to receive them. 

You may notify us of your wish to unsubscribe at any time by: 

• Click on the unsubscribe link shown in all casinobellini.com email offers and follow the instructions.   
• Call us, Tol Free - Canada: +1-800-947-1351   
    UK: 0800-047-0695   
    International phone - +632-756-7946   
• online chat   
• email us to [support@casinobellini.com](mailto:support@casinobellini.com)

On receiving your notice, we will immediately stop sending you such e-mails and updates. 

If you continue to receive from us promotional e-mails and updates or any other unsolicited communication after you have asked us to unsubscribe, please report to us at [abuse@casinobellini.com](mailto:abuse@casinobellini.com). 

## Advertising System

Our advertising system records IP addresses in order to provide more precise characteristics in our site advertising, for instance, banners in a particular language. This system does NOT record any visitor's e-mail address

## Account Creation Information

 **Information collected**

We collect personal information from visitors to this web site through the use of online forms and every time you e-mail us your details. We also collect information about the transactions you undertake including details of payment cards used. The personal information that we collect may include your name, email address, home address, telephone number, debit/credit card data and date of birth and other information collected on registration or through surveys which we, or undertakings engaged by us for such purpose, shall undertake. 

**Use of personal information**

We process your personal information for the purposes of: 

  * (a) creating and managing player accounts and records;
  * (b) administering player accounts;
  * (c) providing and personalising our services;
  * (d) dealing with your enquiries and requests;
  * (e) notifying you about updates to our software and/or services;
  * f) ensuring we are able to fulfill our regulatory responsibilities by verifying the accuracy of any information you give us;
  * (g) our general regulatory compliance, crime prevention and prosecution of offenders including, where appropriate, dealing with requests for information by authorised entities for the sharing of information;
  * (h) carrying out market research campaigns;
  * (i) providing you with information about and support for products and services;
  * (j) marketing our services or products or those of other entities within our group of companies; and
  * (k) supporting any of the intended purposes specifically stated at the time at which you provided the personal information.

These are the **“Purposes”** for which we may collect personal data.

If you do NOT want to receive any e-mail from us, please send us a blank e-mail with the word "remove" in the subject to [support@casinobellini.com](mailto:support@casinobellini.com).

 **Disclosure of personal information**

We may, for the Purposes, disclose your personal information to any of the following recipients (“Recipients”): 

  * (i) any companies within our group and to their employees who have a need to know such information;
  * (ii) any third parties which provide services to us in order to allow or enable us to provide you with gaming services, including by way of example payment processors and data verifiers;
  * (iii) any third parties who provide services to us in relation to the operation of Casino Bellini;
  * (iv) any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of our business processes or who have the need to access such information for the purpose of advising us;
  * (v) any regulatory body or authorised entity who may have any reasonable requirement to access such personal information; and
  * (vi) any potential purchasers of the Casino Bellini business or any investors in it or in any company within our group.

## Use of cookies generally

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on http://www.cookiecentral.com.

We use cookies to identify you when you visit this web site and to keep track of your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile.

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. However, switching off cookies will restrict your ability to make full use of the functionality available on our web site. 

## Winnings

Your winnings and cash-outs are held strictly private, and data on winnings is stored on a secure server. Casino Bellini holds your winnings information private and does not offer this data to any outside party unless such data is mandatory to be divulged by statute, regulation or any governmental or qualified regulatory agency. 

## Security

We keep up the maximum available means to see to it that your data remains secure with us. All data is transmitted using encoding technologies and when stored on our servers, it is kept secure employing the newest firewall software and hardware available today. Our web site and our software employ all accessible methods to keep data accuracy and secrecy and to stop your information from being abused and/or stolen. 

Whenever you have any queries or fears concerning data privacy and protection please contact our Customer Support center at any time, day or night, 7 days a week. Our staff will be happy to help you. 

## Our Certifications and What They Mean

 **Turbo SSL® certificate**  
Casino Bellini (under the name of the casino group) employs a GoDaddy.com Turbo SSL® certificate to guarantee 100% protection and security. A SSL certificate is a digital certificate that confirms the identity of a Web site's owner to a visitor's web browser and encodes data for the web server via Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. GoDaddy.com SSL certificates support both industry-standard 128-bit (used by all banking infrastructures to protect private information) and high-grade 256-bit SSL encryption to protect online transactions. 

## Gaming Laboratories International

 (Click on the logo to view GLI Payout Verification) 

Additionally, all of our games are independently tested by GLI – Gaming Laboratories International. GLI is a large and well-respected firm that carries out independent tests on the fairness and accuracy of casino games. We are proud to display the GLI payout calculation on all of our pages.

Note: all our gaming software is written by Playtech, the leading software provider in the gaming industry. Therefore, the GLI payout calculation letters feature Playtech’s name. As a Playtech client, we use their software without alteration and therefore display this logo and the compliance letter that it links to.
